EPISODE 15
CLOUDS AND RAIN
LIFT
SIDE PLANK
MEITEN HIGH SCHOOL
BANANA DRINK
GENTLE SWEETNESS OF RIPE BANANA
SIP
UH, WHAT?
AM I BEING ATTACKED?
GUILT
WHIRL
SMILE
NO ENTRY
HUH? ME? WHO ARE YOU…?
I FEEL LIKE HE MIGHT BE A GOOD GUY
I GOT DUMPED AGAIN!
FINE, WHATEVER I'LL FORGET ABOUT IT…
IT'S SO OBVIOUS
CRACK
PEOPLE WHO STARTED MINGLING
AT SOME POINT IN THE CHEER SQUAD
OH, REALLY…?
HAHA
DODGING…?
GRADE 2 CLASS 2
ARE YOU OKAY?
DO YOU WANT TO CONSULT ABOUT ANYTHING?
ABOUT YOTA
ABOUT AMAMIYA-KUN
IT'S EMBARRASSING
I WANT TO GET IT OFF MY CHEST
WHAT IF I MAKE HER FEEL AWKWARD?
SOGGY
TEARS WELLING UP
THUMP, THUMP
RANGE OF VOCABULARY DECLINING
ALL MISUNDERSTANDINGS WERE CLEARED UP
SEXUAL DESIRE
CLICKETY CLACKETY
PUFFY EYES
HARD TO DENY
GRADE 2 CLASS 2
PROPERLY SORT TRASH!
FLINCH